Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/nguyen-quang-920a28224 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

React

Redux

Next.js

Nguyen Quang

Senior Software Engineer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I have been a senior web developer for 8+ years in different software companies & teams.

I have solid skills in React/Angular/Vue/bootstrap/material UI/styled components/Nodejs, Express, Postgresql, elasticSearch, docker, React, Redux, Tailwindcss, Nextjs, Gitlab and other technologies.

Experience

Freelance

Senior Software Engineer December 2020 - Present (4 years 4 months)

eCIRCODE Technology
Web Developer
August 2016 - December 2020 (4 years 5 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Bosch

Senior

August 2013 - July 2016 (3 years)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Education

Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology
Engineer's degree, Computer Science, Computer Science · (February 2012 - June 2016)